Come in.
들어와
I've been waiting for you.
기다리고 있었어
Hi, I just
나야, 잠깐...
엄마야!
Oh, my God!
Monica!
세상에, 모 니 카
Oh, my God!
- 망측스러워라
- 저런, 이를 어째
미안하다, 난 그냥
낮잠 좀 자려고
I'm sorry! I was
I was taking a nap.
언제부터 그런 자세로
낮잠을 잤니?
Since when do you
take naps in that position?
Tell me you were waiting for a guy.
Please tell me.
세상에, 제발 남자를
기다리던 중이라고 말해 줘
그래, 맞아
Yes, I was.
A guy.
남자야
From work.
직장 동료
I'm seeing a guy from work!
직장 동료를 만나고 있어, 하!
That cute waiter guy that looks like
a nonthreatening Ray Liotta?
너희 레스토랑의
그 귀여운 웨이터
선량한 레이 리요타처럼 생긴?
아하! 그 사람!
That one!
방해 안 하고 금방 갈게
재킷만 걸치면 되니까
Give me a second.
I'm just going to grab a jacket.
When I get back,
I want every little detail.
내가 돌아오면
속속들이 보고할 것
Maybe that's him.
드디어 오셨구만
저기, 근데...
조이랑 오빠구나
It's just Joey and Ross.
Why aren't you at the movie?
영화 보러 간다더니?
갔는데 로스가 전화통 붙들고
악다구니 쓰는 통에 쫓겨났다
Ross was so loud, they threw us out.
I had to talk loud
because the movie was loud!
어떻게 악다구니를 안 쓰나
영화가 악다구닐 쓰는데
-He's talking to London.
-Did he get in touch with Emily?
런던과 통화 중이야
저런, 에밀리랑
연락 된 거야?
No, not yet. He's hoping that someone
will help him get in touch with her.
아니, 처가 쪽 친척들한테
에밀리 소재를 수소문 중이야
다른 여자 이름 좀 말한 게
무슨 대수냐고, 이 마귀할멈아
I don't care if I said some
other girl's name, you prissy old twit!
로스, 아부 환상적이다
Way to suck up to the family!
I'm so glad you're all here. My office
finally got wrinkle-free fax paper!
마침 다 있었네, 결국 회사에서
구김 없는 팩스용지를 구입했어
The One Where Phoebe Hates PBS
안녕하세요
Hi, is this Nanny Hopkins?
I'm looking for Emily.
내니 홉킨스 되시나요?
에밀리를 찾고 있습니다
Waltham.
월섬이요
죄송합니다, 거기가...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is this 0-1-1-4-4-7-4-2...
011-44-742-934-742-67
아닌가요?
...9-3-4-7-4-2-6-7?
Oh, it's "4-3," not 4-2.
42가 아니라 43라구요
근데 어떤 42죠?
Well, which 4-2?
- 얘들아
- 안 돼, 토한 턱시도야
No, no! Vomit tux!
훠이, 토했어
Don't worry,
I had it dry-cleaned.
걱정 마, 드라이클리닝 했어
Vomit tux?
토한 턱시도?
누가 거기다...
Who vomited on?
You know what?
What you up to, Joe?
그건 그렇고 무슨 일이니?
TV에서 모금방송이 있는데
공동 진행자로 뽑혔지 뭐야
They're doing
this telethon thing on TV.
And my agent
got me a job as cohost!
- 그거 잘됐네
- 멋지다
That's great!
PBS를 위한 선행
더하기, 방송 출연
A little good deed for PBS,
plus some TV exposure.
조이가 좋아하는 산수지
That's the kind of math
Joey likes to do.
오! PBS...
Oh, PBS!
- PBS가 뭐 잘못됐니?
- 잘된 건 뭐 있어?
-What's wrong with PBS?
-What's right with them?
Why don't you like PBS?
왜 PBS를 싫어하지?
엄마가 자살하신 후
내가 좀 엉망으로 살았잖니
Right after my Mom killed herself,
I was in a bad place, personally.
알다시피 개인적으로
그래서...
'세서미 스트리트'에 편지를
쓰면 위로가 될 것 같더라
I thought I'd write
to Sesame Street.
Because they were nice
when I was a little kid.
그땐 참 착해 보였거든
No one ever wrote back.
근데 답장이 안 왔어
A lot of those muppets
don't have thumbs.
머펫들은 대개 엄지가 없잖아
달랑 열쇠고리 하나 받았어
All I got was a lousy key chain, and
by that time, I was living in a box.
박스를 집 삼아 살았는데
무슨 키가 있다고!
I didn't have keys!
미안하다, 난 그냥...
I'm sorry, Phoebe.
I wanted to do a good deed,
like you did with the babies.
좋은 일을 하고 싶었어
네가 아기를 낳은 것처럼
네 일은 달라
This isn't a good deed. You just
want to get on TV. This is selfish.
방송 타려는 거잖아
이기적인 행동이지
이거 봐라?
What about you having
those babies for your brother?
남동생 아기를 낳은 애가
누구한테 이기적이래?
That's selfish!
What are you talking about?
그게 무슨 소리야?
물론 좋은 일이었지만
너도 뿌듯했잖아
It was a nice thing,
but it made you feel good, right?
Yeah, so?
맞아, 그런데?
네 가슴도 뿌듯했으니
이기적인 거 아냐?
It made you feel good
so that makes it selfish.
Look, there's no
unselfish good deeds. Sorry.
안 됐지만 이기심을
배제한 선행은 없어
Yes, there are totally
good deeds that are selfless!
없긴 왜 없어
이타적인 선행도 있어
예 하나만 들어볼래?
May I ask for one example?
Yeah, it's
You know, there's
그래, 까짓 거 뭐...
알잖아, 그게...
아니, 들기 싫어
No, you may not!
Because all people are selfish.
사람은 다 이기적이니까
Are you calling me selfish?
나도 이기적인가?
Are you calling you people?
넌 사람 아니냐?
환상을 깨서 미안하지만
이타적인 선행은 없는 거야
Sorry to burst that bubble, Phoebe,
but selfless good deeds don't exist.
You know the deal
on Santa Claus?
산타클로스와의 계약 알지?
I'll find a selfless good deed.
I'm going to beat you, you evil genius!
그런 선행을 찾아내서 네 코를
뭉개주겠어, 이 사악한 천재야
여보세요?
로스?
에밀리?
이런, 에밀리 전화야!
다들 시끄러, 쉬쉬쉬!
Oh, my God! It's Emily!
It's Emily, everyone!
안녕?
I'm only ringing to say
stop harassing my relatives. Goodbye.
내 친척들 괴롭히지 말라고
전화한 거야, 잘 있어
잠깐, 끊으려면 끊어
난 계속 전화할 거야
You can hang up, but I'll keep calling
everyone in England...
영국사람 전부라도 상관없어
자기랑 얘기할 수만 있다면
...if that's what it takes
to get you to talk to me.
Really? About what?
무슨 얘기?
자기는 내 아내야
우린 결혼했다고
Look, you're my wife.
We're married.
자기를 사랑해
You know, I love you.
I really miss you.
정말 보고 싶어
나도 자기가 그리워
I miss you too.
At least, I think I do.
그런 것 같아
She's talking.
얘기하고 있어
산타클로스와의 계약이
무슨 뜻이지?
When you said "the deal with Santa,"
you meant...?
산타클로스는 없다고
That he doesn't exist.
Right.
맞아
Chandler, have you heard
about Monica's secret boyfriend?
챈들러, 모니카가
숨겨둔 애인 알아?
그래, 들은 것도 같네
Yeah, she might have mentioned him.
So, Mon, when are we going
to meet this new, secret waiter man?
베일에 싸인 웨이터는
언제 보여줄 거야?
I don't think he's
up to meeting everyone yet.
수줍음이 많은 사람이라
아직은 곤란할 것 같아
그래, 아직은 곤란하지
Yeah, I don't think he's up to it.
어떤 남자가 모니카
최고의 섹스 상대였을까?
I want to meet this guy
who's the best sex she ever had.
Really?
증말?!
That's what you heard?
You said that?
그런 말을 들었나?
그렇게 얘기했나?
그랬을 거야
I might have.
뭐가 그렇게 웃겨?
Why is that funny?
Because I'm very happy for him.
그 친구가 장해서
And you!
You lucky dog!
너도 복 터진 거야
- 안녕?
- 어서 와
She's willing to work
on the relationship.
에밀리가 노력해보겠대
That's great!
- 잘됐다
- 그래
- 런던에서
- 뭐?
In London.
She wants me to move to London.
런던으로 거처를 옮기래
오빤 여기 살잖아
But you live here.
You know that.
알고 있구나
어떡할 거야?
-What will you do?
-I don't know.
모르겠어, 어떻게
벤을 두고 떠나니?
-I mean, I can't leave Ben.
-You can just video-conference with him.
화상회의로 하면 되지
I'm not ready to have a child.
난 당분간 백수로 지낼래
I bet if I talked to Carol and Susan...
캐롤이랑 수잔한테 얘기하면
분명 벤하고 같이 와줄 거야
...I could convince them
to move to London with Ben.
I'm sure your ex-wife
would be more than happy to move...
오빠 새 부인이랑 화해하라고
전처가 외국으로 이사를 간대?
...so you can patch things up
with your new wife.
It could happen.
못 갈 거 없지
Ross, we are not moving to London.
We already have lives here.
런던으로는 못 간다니까
여기 생활은 어떡하고?
재미있을 거야
근사한 극장에 근사한 억양
But it'd be great.
They have great theater...
...great accents.
Tea.
차는 어때?
여왕도 있어
They have a queen.
-So?
-She's a woman.
- 그래서?
- 여자잖아
나 왔어
- 아빠!
- 이 녀석!
-Daddy!
-Hey!
Guess what? We're moving to London!
우리 런던으로 이사 간다!
-Who's going to London?
-Nobody's going to London.
- 누가 런던에 가는데?
- 가긴 누가 가
Welcome to London, governor.
런던에 잘 오셨네요, 총독님
Right, right. It'll be great
because we'll have Big Ben and little Ben...
로이, 로이...
멋지잖아요, 빅 벤과
리틀 벤이 한 도시에
...in the same city.
뭐해, 어서 짐 싸
Go pack!
See? See, he wants to go.
봤죠? 애도 가겠다잖아요
네, 중대한 결정은
세 살짜리가 다 하죠
Yeah, we leave all our big decisions
to the 3-year-old.
Come on, come on.
It'll be just like Three's Company...
이러지 말아요
셋도 짝이 될 수 있죠
단지 아이 하나와
그리고 내 아내
...only there's a kid and my wife...
두 사람은 동성애자고
...and you're the gay ones.
유니텔 비디오
스튜디오 55
안녕하세요, 환영합니다
반갑습니다
How you doing? Welcome.
Good to see you.
이 전화를 쓰세요
This'll be your phone.
고맙긴 하지만...
That's great.
But I'm not really
expecting a lot of calls.
전화 올 일 별로 없는데
아뇨, 기부자들의
전화를 받아야 해요
No, you answer it
and take pledges.
But I'm the host.
전 진행자인데요
진행자는 개리 콜린스고
댁은 전화를 받으세요
Gary Collins is the host.
You'll be answering the phone.
You don't seem to understand.
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray.
잘 모르시는 모양인데
난 드레이크 라모레 박사였어요
전화 여기 있어요, 박사님
Well, here's your phone, doctor.
I can't believe I can't find
a selfless good deed.
이타적인 선행을
찾을 수 없다니
You know that old guy
that lives next to me?
우리 이웃에 살던
할아버지 있었지?
내가 몰래 그 집에 가서
현관 앞에 낙엽을 모아놓으면
I snuck over there and raked up
the leaves on his front stoop.
날 잡아서 억지로
과자랑 음료수를 먹였어
But he caught me, and he
force-fed me cider and cookies.
Then I felt wonderful.
That old jackass!
기분은 째지더라
망할 영감탱이
어쩜 조이 말대로 모든
선행은 이기적인지도 몰라
Maybe Joey's right.
Maybe all good deeds are selfish.
난 이타적인 선행을
찾아낼 거야
I will find a selfless good deed.
I gave birth to three children...
내가 낳은 애들이 조이가 옳은
세상에서 살게 할 순 없으니까
...and I won't let them be raised
in a world where Joey's right!
모니카
Can I ask you a cooking question?
- 요리법 하나 물어볼까?
- 그래
네가 스토브로 요리를 한다면
If you're cooking on the stove...
...that means your new boyfriend
is better in bed than Richard?
새 남자친구가 리처드보다
침대에서 낫다는 뜻일까?
챈들러...
Is he?
그래?
이제 내 남자친구에 대해
프라이버시를 지켜야겠다
I think I'll respect the privacy
of my new, secret boyfriend.
왜?
Why?
If this guy was me...
만약 그 친구가 나고
내가 너한테 최고의 남자라는
사실을 안다면
...and it's me who'd learned that it was
me who was the best you'd ever had...
...I'd be like this:
난 이렇게 나올 거야
All right, Emily.
에밀리
자기를 많이 사랑하지만
As much as I love you...
미안해, 벤 없이는
런던으로 갈 수 없어
...I'm sorry, I can't
move to London without Ben.
I understand that would be difficult.
힘들다는 거 이해해
자기가 여기로 올 순 없을까?
Would you consider moving here?
You were moving here anyway.
원래 이쪽으로 올 생각이었잖아
Why can't you just do that?
I don't know. It's just
모르겠어, 그냥...
좋아, 하지만...
난 알아, 내가 지금까지
바보짓만 골라 했어도
But I know that even though I've been
a complete idiot up till now...
...you have to come here.
자기는 꼭 이리 와야 돼
와서 함께 해결하자고
You have to, so we can
work this out together.
좋아
All right.
좋아? 방금 좋다고 했어?
Did you just say "all right"?
그래, 이제 내가 바보야
I did.
Now I'm the idiot.
Emily, that is so great!
에밀리, 정말 잘 생각했어
그렇고 말고
It'll be great!
우리 둘 다 사랑에 빠진
바보가 되는 거야
We're going to be
like two idiots in love!
로스, 그래도 아직
두려운 게 있어
There's one thing that
really scares me still.
뭔데, 말해봐
-Yes, tell me.
-You must understand...
그게 하객들 앞에서 얼마나
수치스러운 일인지 잘 알잖아
...how humiliating it was
for me at the altar...
...in front of my family and friends.
I know. I am so sorry.
알아, 정말 미안해
그래도 난 자길 용서했는데
And then, after deciding
to forgive you...
...seeing you at the airport,
catching our plane with her.
공항에서 레이첼과
우리 비행기를 타려 했어
Again, very sorry.
또 한 번 진심으로 죄송해요
I mean, I can't be
in the same room as her.
난 레이첼이 될 수 없어
It drives me mad thinking of you
being in the same room as her.
날 레이첼로 생각했다면
정말 화나는 일이잖아
나와 레이첼은 아무
사이도 아냐, 알았지?
Emily, there is nothing
between Rachel and me.
난 당신을 사랑해
I love you.
좋아
All right.
뉴욕으로 가서 함께 노력해볼게
I'll come to New York,
and we'll try to make this work.
그럼 정말 좋지
That's so great!
As long as you
don't see Rachel anymore.
다시는 레이첼을
안 본다고 약속하면
I asked Emily
if she would come to New York.
에밀리한테 뉴욕으로
와달라고 했더니
And she said yes.
좋다고 했어
- 그렇지!
- 잘됐다
Great!
잠시 대기
Only if I promise
never to see Rachel again.
레이첼을 두 번 다시
안 본다는 조건으로
What? You can't
- 뭐? 그게...
- 저런
What did you say?
오빤 뭐라고 했어?
I'd think about it. How am l
supposed to make this decision?
생각해본다고 했지, 어떻게
내가 그런 결정을 내리겠어?
I'm actually asking you!
묻고 있잖아!
어떻게 레이첼을 안 봐?
둘도 없는 친구인데
Rachel is one of your best friends.
- 맞아
- 그래
그렇다고 부인인 에밀리를
안 볼 수도 없잖아
But Emily's his wife!
That's true!
- 사실이야
- 맞아, 그래
하지만 고교 때부터 알던
친구와 그렇게 절교할 순 없어
You can't just cut Rachel
out of your life!
That's true!
- 것도 그래!
- 안 되지
Thanks for the help.
Problem solved!
협조 고맙다, 문제 해결
여보세요
- 안녕, 모니카
- 조이니?
종일 TV 보는데 넌 안 나와
When will you be on TV?
There was kind of a mix-up
in my agent's office...
에이전시에서 뭔가
혼동을 한 모양인데
...but I'm still on TV,
and that's good exposure.
나 지금 TV에
똑똑히 나오고 있어
You're not on TV.
안 보이는데?
알았어, 지금은 어때?
How about now?
그래, 저기 있다!
There he is!
헬로, 뉴욕!
Hello, New York!
오리는 통째로 넣어도
상관없습니다
Maybe just put the whole duck in there.
Who cares?
이제 다리 부위
Now I got the legs.
How many times have I told you
to never watch the cooking channel?
요리 채널 시청 금지라고
몇 번을 말해야 되니?
- 챈들러
- 그래
전에 조이가 빌려 간
냄비 가지러 왔어
I need that broiling pan
that Joey borrowed.
That was yours?
너희 거였니?
그건 오리가 벌레
토할 때 써버렸는데
We used it when the duck
was throwing up caterpillars.
Williams-Sonoma,
fall catalog, page 27.
윌리엄스 소노마
가을 카탈로그 27페이지
4~6주 후에 도착 예정
Expect it in 4 to 6 weeks.
저기, 조이는 종일
방송국에 있을 테니까
Joey's at the telethon
for the rest of the day.
We have the place to ourselves.
- 이 집은 비거든
- 그래서?
Yeah, so?
혹시 최고의 시간을
예약해볼 생각은 없냐고
Maybe you'd want to book some time
with "the best you've ever had."
You know what, champ?
이거 아니, 잘난 양반?
I think I'll pass.
사양할게
Why?
- 왜?
- 왜냐고?
What's your point?
요점이 뭐야?
With all the stupid gloating,
would you want to sleep with you?
그 바보짓을 해놓고
너랑 자길 바래?
Well, I think I'd be a little out of my league,
but I'd give it a shot.
약간은 무리가 따르지만
시도는 해볼래
PBS Telethon.
PBS 모금방송입니다
I just wanted to let you know
that I found a selfless good deed.
안녕, 조이
방금 이타적인 선행을
찾아냈지 뭐니
I went down to the park
and I let a bee sting me.
주차장으로 내려오다
벌이 날 쏘게 했거든
What good is that going to do?
뭐? 그게 선행이야?
친구 앞에서 젠체하는
벌한테는 좋지
It helps the bee look tough
in front of his bee friends.
The bee is happy,
and I am definitely not.
그 벌은 행복하겠지만
난 전혀 아냐
You know, the bee probably
died after he stung you.
그 벌은 침을 쏘고
죽었을 거야
Damn it!
돌겠네!
Back on in 30 seconds, people!
30초 후에 들어갑니다
Excuse me,
would you mind switching with me?
실례합니다
자리 좀 바꿀까요?
난 저쪽인데
No way.
I'm in the shot, man.
거긴 안 잡히잖아요
-You've been here all day!
-I'm taking pledges.
- 여기 종일 있었으면서
- 전화 좀 받읍시다
And we're on three, two....
준비하세요
셋, 둘...
Welcome back to our fall telethon.
춘계모금방송입니다
If you've been enjoying
Cirque du Soleil...
태양극단의 공연이
마음에 드시고
...and you'd like to see more,
it's very simple.
이런 종류의 프로그램을
더 원하신다면
방법은 간단합니다
All you have to do
is call in a pledge...
전화로 소정의 기부금을
약속하시면서
...and tell one of our volunteers
what type of programming you
연결된 저희 자원봉사자에게
원하는 프로그램을 말씀하세요
냄비에 대한 질문 받나?
-Quick broiling pan question
-Yes, it really does cost that much.
가격은 그대로야, 다음 번에
토할 땐 쌈지막한 그릇을 내줘
Maybe next time your duck can puke
in something from Pottery Barn.
안 되겠어, 난 못해
너무 어려운 결정이야
That's it. I cannot make this decision.
It is too difficult.
I leave it entirely
up to the gods of fate.
운명의 신에게
모든 걸 맡기겠어
A Magic 8 Ball?
마법의 에잇볼?
You can't make this decision
with a toy!
말도 안 돼, 장난감으로
운명을 결정한다고?
장난감이 아냐
It's not a toy.
다른 수가 없잖아
I don't know what else to do!
I either keep my wife
and lose one of my best friends...
아내를 선택하고
절친한 친구를 버리든가
아니면 친구를 선택하고
...or I get divorced
for the second time before I'm 30.
서른 되기 전에 두 번
이혼하는 남자가 되든가
If anyone else has
a better suggestion, let's hear it.
너희한테 더 좋은 생각이
있다면 한번 들어보자
난 도무지 모르겠어
Because I got nothing!
Don't be shy.
어떤 거라도 좋으니까
빼지 말고 얘기들 해봐
Any suggestion will do.
Okay, then.
그럼 좋아
Here we go.
시작할게
Magic 8 Ball...
마법의 에잇볼아, 다시는
레이첼을 안 봐야할까?
...should I never see Rachel again?
"Ask Again Later."
'나중에 질문하세요'
나중에 물어보라면 장땡이냐?
Later is not good enough!
"Ask Again Later."
'나중에 질문하... '
What the hell?
환장하겠네
이거 고장났어!
This is broken! It is broken!
Let me see.
어디 한번 봐
Will Chandler have sex tonight?
챈들러가 오늘밤
섹스를 할까요?
"Don't Count On lt."
'꿈도 꾸지 마세요'
Seems like it works to me.
좋아, 한 번 더
Okay, one more time.
다시는 레이첼을
보지 말아야 하나요?
Should I never see Rachel again?
얘들아
Magic 8 Ball! What did you ask?
오, 마법의 에잇볼
뭘 물었는데?
오늘밤 우리가 볼 영화를
레이첼이 고르게 할까요?
Does...
...Rachel get to pick the movie
that we're all going to see tonight?
좋았어, 대답은?
Excellent. What's the answer?
야호! '오늘밤 그녀의
감각이 돌아온다네'
Looks like Stella's gonna get
her groove back tonight!
What? I heard it was good.
왜, 재미있다던데
PBS Telethon.
PBS 모금방송입니다
Hi, Joey.
- 나야, 조이
- 그래, 피비
Hey, Phoebe.
기부금을 내고 싶어
I'd like
to make a pledge.
I would like to donate $200.
2백 달러로 할게
Two hundred dollars?
2백 달러라, 진심이야?
세서미 스트리트는 어쩌고?
You sure?
After what Sesame Street did to you?
아직도 화는 나지만
I'm still mad at them,
but they bring happiness...
자살하지 않은 엄마를 둔
아이들을 행복하게 해주잖아
...to lots of kids
whose moms didn't kill themselves.
그 애들을 돕는 건 선행이지만
난 '행복하지' 않아
By supporting them, I'm doing a good
thing, but I'm not happy about it.
So there!
A selfless good deed.
바로 이타적인 선행이지
기부하는 게 전혀
즐겁지 않다?
You don't feel good
about donating the money?
No, it sucks!
I was saving up to buy a hamster.
기분 꽝이야
햄스터 사려고 모은 돈인데
햄스터? 그런 건
10달러면 사잖아
A hamster?
Those things are, like, $10.
내가 봐둔 건 아냐
Not the one I had my eye on.
작년의 모금 총액을
넘어선 것 같군요
It looks like we have surpassed
last year's pledge total.
Thank you!
감사합니다
And the pledge that did it
was taken by one of our volunteers.
이 기부금을 받은
저희 자원봉사자는...
Oh, boy! And may I say,
one of our sharpest dressed volunteers.
이런, 가장 번듯하게
빼입은 자원봉사자군요
조셉 트리비아니 씨
Mr. Joseph Tribbiani!
Oh, look!
봐, 조이가 TV에 나왔어
너무 근사하지?
Joey's on TV!
Isn't that great?
내 기부금 덕분에
조이가 방송을 탔어
My pledge got Joey on TV!
That makes me feel so
기분 죽인다... 안 돼!
Oh, no!
Look...
모니카, 아까는 내가
잠시 흥분했었지만
...I got carried away before,
but there's something you got to know.
이것만은 알아줘
If I'm the best, it's only
because you made me the best.
만약 내가 최고였다면
그건 네가 날 최고로
만들어준 덕분이야
Keep talking.
계속해 봐
I was nothing before you.
예전에 난 아무 것도 아니었어
Call the other girls and ask.
딴 여자들한테
전화해서 물어봐
Which wouldn't take long.
오래 걸리지도 않아
But when I'm with you,
and we're together...
하지만 너랑 있으면...
너와 함께 있으면
오... 마이... 갓이야
...oh, my God!
-Really?
-Oh, my God!
- 진짜?
- 오 마이 갓
이제 나랑 안 잔다니까
하는 말인데
I understand if you never
want to sleep with me again.
잘 못 생각한 거야
우린 너무 좋았어
But that would be wrong.
We're too good.
우린 빚을 졌어
섹스한테!
We owe it to sex!
If we owe it!
빚은 갚아야지
Oh, my!
오 마이...
조이는 언제 온대?
When will Joey be home?
I was kind of hoping
we could do this without him.
그 녀석 없이 해보고 싶어
알았어
그래, 좋아
No, no, no!
Leave the gloves on.
아냐, 그냥 끼고 있어
I cleaned the bathroom.
방금 화장실 청소했는데?
Why don't we lose the gloves.
그럼 벗어버려
All right.
Let's show them how it's done.
- 좋아, 본때를 보여주자
- 그래
아우!
-You know that wasn't part of it?
-I know.
이건 빼는 거야
- 알아
- 고럼!
나야, 준비됐니?
이러다 늦어
You ready?
We're going to be late.
-For what?
-For Stella, remember?
뭐가?
스텔라 말이야, 잊었어?
20분 후부터
감각이 돌아올 텐데
She's getting her groove back
in 20 minutes.
I totally forgot about that.
그래, 까맣게 잊고 있었네
다음에 가면 안 될까?
에밀리가 전화한다고 해서
Can I take a rain check?
I'm waiting for a call from Emily.
Sure, I guess.
그래, 알았어
I hear you don't have to
go to London.
런던에 안 가도 된다며?
It's not that easy. There's still
a lot of relationship stuff.
그렇게 단순하지 않아
문제가... 얽히고설켜서
- 어떻게?
- 그냥 뭐...
Like what?
Just stuff.
You know, kind of what Emily wants.
에밀리가 원하는 것도
있고 해서
얘기해 봐, 내가 도와줄게
Talk to me.
Maybe I can help.
아냐, 넌...
도와줄 수 없어
You can't help.
이번 일은...
I have to do this
without your help.
네 도움 없이 해결해야 돼
난 그냥...
I know you can do that too.
I'm just saying if you need to talk....
혼자서도 할 수 있겠지만
얘기나 들어주고 싶어서
나야!
고맙다
Thanks.
로스
지금 에밀리가 뭘 원하든
그렇게 해줘
Whatever it is that Emily wants...
...just give it to her.
The bottom line is that you love her.
어쨌든 넌 에밀리를 사랑하잖아
Fix whatever she wants fixed.
바꾸길 원한다면 뭐든 바꿔
Just do it.
하는 거야
You're going to have to try.
You'll hate yourself if you don't.
노력은 해야지
나중에 후회하지 말고
Come on, answer it!
빨리 받아
어지럽다
여보세요
Hi, sweetie.
그래, 자기야
Good.
좋아
저기...
Yes, I've been thinking...
그럼, 생각해봤지
자기가 원하는 대로...
...about that thing
you wanted me to do.
I can do it.
한번 해볼게
Will you come to New York?
그럼 뉴욕으로 오는 거야?
뭐야?
잘했어
-Never done that before.
-Nope.
- 그런 거 처음이야?
- 그럼